It may not look like it, but this is one of London's coolest alternative fashion stores.
Come along.
Hey!
Welcome to Turf School!
Thanks!
I'm in London at the Charm School showroom and I am blown away by the variety of outfits
and designers that can be found here.
So I'm going to try some on and take you with me.
So we got Rose Noir designs.
It's hand poured latex sheets and I think the colors are really amazing.
Also the blue ones.
unique designs and I think I am going to try on this jacket.
It's too soon to care, it's too late to change
Picture this
Lying on the grass at sunset counting stars
I think about it all the time
So I heard that these are some of the best sellers and that I'm lucky that they're in stock
so I'm going to try this one on top of my outfit
So this is Lorna Jane harnesses and it's super lightweight.
It doesn't look like it but you won't even feel it when you wear it all night for a party.
It's just really comfy and it looks so awesome.
It's too soon to care, but too late to change
Too soon to care, but too late to change
I feel like this anxiety is pulling me in front of you
It's building up inside of me with everything
I have seen these quite a few times already with these big ass rivets now.
So of course I need to try one and look at that O-ring.
I'm standing at the door
We're trying to be strong
I wanna say I love you
But it feels wrong
I'm worried what will happen next
But I guess I'll wait
So
This is a resin corset.
It's actually solid.
And I think it looks just amazing.
Also the back.
I paired it with a choker and a matching bracelet.
So it's a very great look.
Welcome.
How are you?
Good.
So before I get dressed again,
I want to try on this set.
And it's really heavy.
Actually the skirt was too small,
but I think the jacket itself is so awesome.
It's by Painkiller clothing.
These are show pieces
and they're one of the most exclusive brands
here at Charm School.
I just love this look.
It's really heavy because of all the rivets.
It's really nice and like it's creams with the neon green.
I paired it with a belt
and I think it's just such great look.
Bummer that the skirt doesn't fit,
but it works with the leggings as well.
Enchanted by your spells
Lost within your eyes
Home amongst your words
I'm going straight to hell
I just found pieces by Amentium Latex.
I've walked for her on a show and she's well known for these laser cutouts and bright colors
and intricate designs.
So this is the men's selection actually.
They have great options for men too and I know it's always a bit hard to find something
as a guy.
I saw a jacket I'm going to try on myself because I think it's really cool.
So I get an impression.
I think it's a small size because it fits me rather good.
I just found these PVC coats and I think I have to try one.
And never really find
With me is Alexandra, the owner of Charm School.
Thanks for having me today.
Oh, you're so welcome.
How long is the store open already?
So we actually only opened in February.
And fun fact, we had nine days to get the store open.
We found the spot really last minute.
And then we had to go through all the paperwork over Christmas.
Then we had to find all the designers, buy everything for the inside of the store and open in nine days.
It was crazy.
I saw it on Instagram and my London friends visited.
And so I was like, I have to stop by because it's just so awesome.
And I love the variation of designers you have.
How many designers do you display here?
Well, on our website, we had about 150.
We've been slowly narrowing it down because we found actually the customers prefer to have less selection rather than more selection.
In the store, it can be anywhere between 30 and 50.
We often just get sometimes like a small exclusive drop from people that has a few pieces.
And then we have regular designers who always have a presence in the store.
But it fluctuates between 30 and 50.
So there's always a lot of choice.
What kind of look is your personal favorite?
Well, I'm quite a colorful girl.
so yeah so not everything in here is my exact cup of tea but I really appreciate the dark style and
people who love to wear all black but we like to have something for everybody so personal favorites
would be hard to choose but Lucien who's behind me is one of my babies a designer I've been working
with since she started out and yeah she she's probably one of my favorites but there's so many
great brands in here it would be hard to say okay so why should people stop by well we'd like to
offer an escape from the sad, cold world outside. I mean, the world is a sad place these days. There's
a lot of bad things happening. And in here is a place where we can be joyful. We can appreciate
handmade products that are made by nice people. Everything is sustainable. We can celebrate our
bodies and our diversity. We're kind to each other. We're kind to ourselves. And who doesn't
like to play dress up? I had a dressing up box when I was little. And I think now I just grew
and have a giant dressing up box.
Oh, that's so good.
I can totally feel that.
So yeah, thanks again.
It's wonderful here.
I love it.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Yeah, so we really like to have something for everybody.
It's our mission to like,
no matter what your style is with an alternative fashion,
we can offer something.
We love to give really personalized service.
We love to help people find the right outfit.
We have a lot of people who are taking their first steps
into alternative fashion
and they can come in and have no idea
what they're looking for.
And we're here to help.
We're here to sit down, have a cup of tea, chat with people what they're looking for and have them leave feeling amazing.
So it's the best job in the world.
I love it. But there's also a website where people can order the pieces, right?
Yes. So the website is an online marketplace.
So if you've ever used Depop or Etsy, it's quite similar.
So the sellers have their own shop within our shopping mall.
You enter our shopping mall, you discover all the shops.
You can communicate directly with the designers about whatever it is that you want.
If you like this, but you want it in red and black or a different size, they can make that happen for you.
And then they make the order in their own studio or workshop and they post it to you directly.
So as a last look, what would you give me to wear?
Oh, it's so hard to decide because there's so many treats in here.
But I'm going to have to go with a Lucien corset, one of our best selling items.
People love them because they're very versatile.
You can work them in with your wardrobe, wear a cool biker jacket or maybe a pencil skirt, your favorite leggings.
so I have to say I'm quite in love with this silver corset and I feel like it would be a
really good look so I'm thinking silver corset and then some jewelry from our best-selling
jewelry brand 666999. Okay let's go. I think this is a great outfit and combination with the choker
and the corset just love how this looks and with that spectacular outfit I hope you enjoyed this
video check out charm school instagram web page if you're in london stop by here to go shopping
because it's just really awesome there's so many cool items here and yeah i wish you a nice day
check out the links in the description text and my socials see you around in the next video have a
nice day bye